ILGWU. Out of business contracts, 5780/158
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILGWU. Out of Business contracts
1988-1998.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union.
5780/158
6.5 cubic feet
6.5 linear feet
Contracts
This collection consists of contracts between the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union and defunct garment manufacturing firms.
5510877
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff
Date completed:
1998
EAD encoding:
Casey Westerman, 2003Cheryl Beredo, July 2011
Biographical / Historical
The International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union was founded in New York City in 1900 by mostly Socialist immigrant workers who sought to unite the various crafts in the growing women's garment industry. The union soon reflected changes in the sector and rapidly organized thousands of unskilled and semi-skilled women, mostly Jewish and Italian young immigrants. Exemplifying the "new unionism," the ILGWU led two of the most widespread and best-known industrial strikes of the early Twentieth Century: the shirtwaist makers' strike of 1909 in New York City and the cloak makers' strike of 1910 in Chicago. The union also tried to adapt to the fragmented and unstable nature of the industry. It adopted the "protocol of peace," a system of industrial relations that attempted to ensure stability and limit strikes and production disruption by providing for an arbitration system to resolve disputes.
The ILGWU exemplified the European-style social unionism of its founding members. They pursued bread and butter issues but provided educational opportunities, benefits, and social programs to union members as well. In 1919, the ILGWU became the first American union to negotiate an unemployment compensation fund that was contributed to by its employers. The ILGWU also pioneered in the establishment of an extremely progressive health care program for its members which included not only regional Union Health Centers but also a resort for union workers, known as Unity House. The Union also had an imaginative and pioneering Education Department which not only trained workers in traditional union techniques, but provided courses in citizenship and the English language.
David Dubinsky, an immigrant from Belarus who came to the US in 1911, provided strong leadership that led to unprecedented growth in the union during his presidency from 1932 to 1966. He led the union through successful internal anti-communist struggles, built on the ascendancy of industrial unionism by encouraging the formation of the Committee for Industrial Organization, and helped the union become an important political force in New York City and state politics, and in the national Democratic Party and Liberal Party as well.
In the period following the Second World War, the union suffered a decline in membership as manufacturers avoided unionization and took advantage of less expensive labor by moving shops from the urban centers in the northeast to the south, and later abroad. The ethnic and racial character of the ILGWU also changed as European immigrants were supplanted by Asians, Latin Americans, African- Americans, and immigrants from the Caribbean.
In July 1995 the ILGWU merged with the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union (ACTWU) at a joint convention, forming UNITE (Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees). At the time the new union had a membership of about 250,000 in the United States, Canada, and Puerto Rico.
Scope and Contents
This collection consists of contracts between the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union and defunct garment manufacturing firms.
Conditions Governing Access
The ILGWU Records, except for publications and materials produced for publication, are restricted. Materials created prior to twenty years from the current date are open to researchers only with prior written permission from the Director of the Kheel Center; materials created during the past twenty-years are closed; the minutes of the General Executive Board are closed. For more information contact the Kheel Center.
Related Materials
5780. ILGWU records
5780/075. ILGWU. Collective Bargaining Agreements
5780/075 mf. ILGWU. Collective Bargaining Agreements. Microfilm
5780/085. ILGWU. National War Labor Board case files
5780/145. ILGWU. Association Agreements. Out-of-Business Contracts
5780/146. ILGWU. Master Agreements. Out-of-Business Contracts
5780/147. ILGWU. Independents. Out-of-Business Contracts
5780/191. ILGWU. Association Contracts
5780/202. ILGWU. Operations Department. Collective Bargaining Agreements
General
"Permanent deposit"
Women's clothing industry--United States.; Labor unions--Clothing workers--United States.; Clothing workers--United States.; Industrial relations--United States.; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union.; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union.; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Midwest Region.
5510877
- Convention Collective de Travail, 1993-1995 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  In French
- Agreement Between A.H. Schreiber Company and Philadelphia/South Jersey District Council, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- A and L Pleating Company Agreement, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Alfar Imports Agreement, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Allura Agreement, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Amcan-Charter Imports, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Bargaining Agreement with Amelia Dress and Locals 224, 236, and 238 Southern District Council of the Upper South Department, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- American Bazaar International, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Agreement Between Andrea Sportswear and Local 120, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Collective Bargaining Agreement Between Angelair Bridal Manufacturing and Locals 5, 81, and 100, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Collective Bargaining Agreement Between Locals of New Jersey Region and Angel Knitwear, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Agreement Between Arbe/Hilson and Missouri-Mississippi River Valley District Council, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Beatriz Esparza DBA Contractors, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Berkley Uniforms and Local 76 Agreement, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Agreement Between Board of Directors of Connecticut Peace Action (CPA) on behalf of Peace Action Education Fund (PAEF) and Local 151, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Borg Textile Corporation Agreement, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Agreement Between Boris Smoler and Sons and Local 76, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Agreement Between Brand Mills/Venture Lace and Local 145, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Agreement Between Bridal Originals and Missouri-Mississippi River Valley District Council, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Agreement Between Brockton School Committee and Local 242, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Agreement Between Brockton School Committee and Local 242, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Agreement Between Bestform and Local 424, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Agreement Between Bestform and Local 424, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Agreement Between Bestform and Local 424, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Agreement Between Bestform and Local 424, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Agreement Between Bestform and Local 424, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Agreement Between Brookshire Knitting Mills and Texas-Oklahoma-Arkansas District Council, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Agreement between Brown-Service Funeral Homes Company and Local 479, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Supplemental Agreement Between Calvin Klein/Calvin Klein Sport/Paul Modes and ILGWU, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Agreement Between Camden Tanning Corporation and Local Union 75, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Agreement Between Camden Tanning Corporation and Local Union 533, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Collective Agreement Between Local 286 and Canadian Classique Inc, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Agreement between Apparel America for Itself on behalf of its Capitol Swimwear Plant and Local 151 of Unite, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Agreement between Apparel America for Itself on behalf of its Capitol Swimwear Plant and Local 151, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Agreement Between Capitol Swimwear and Local 153, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Collective Bargaining Agreement Between Carla Gay Dress Company and ILGWU, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Collective Bargaining Agreement Between Carollton Clothing Company and Local 578, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Memorandum of Agreement Between Charland Sportswear Corporation and Local 445, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Agreement Between Chicago Trading Corporation and Local 336, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Agreement Between Chow Sportswear and Joint Board of Cloak, Skirt, and Dressmakers Union, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Agreement between Local 151 and Church Street South Limited Partnership, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Agreement Between Classic Fashions and Local 601, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Agreement between Cleveland Knitting Mills and Ohio District Council, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Agreement Between Cleveland Knitting Mills and Ohio District Council, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Agreement between Cleveland Knitting Mills and Ohio District Council, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Agreement Between Clover Yarns and Local 403, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Agreement between Clever Maid Uniform Manufacturing Company and Local 76, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Collective Bargaining Agreement Between Coastal Industries and Local 516, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Agreement between Colebrook/Terry and Locals 108, 196, and 197, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Agreement Between Columbus Sportswear Company and Local 444, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Collective Agreement with Confection du Lac Inc, 1993-1996 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Agreement Between Conrad Stitching and Embroidery Inc and Quebec Joint Council, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Agreement between Conrad Stitching and Embroidery Inc and Quebec Joint Council, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Bargaining Agreement between Crewe Garment Company and Local 504, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Bargaining Agreement between Crewe Garment Company and Local 504, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Agreement between Cricket Sportswear and Joint Board of Cloak, Skirt, and Dressmakers Union, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Agreement between Crystal Brands/Jane and Linda Sportswear and Local 472, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Collective Bargaining Agreement between Dawson Home Fashions and Local 299, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Collective Bargaining Agreement between Dawson Home Fashions and Local 551, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Collective Bargaining Agreement between Hygiene Industries and Local 551, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Agreement between Denim Finishers and Local 430, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Collective Labor Agreement between Doe-Spun Inc and ILGWU, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Agreement between El Ponce de Leon Convalescent Center and Local 415-475, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Agreement between El Ponce de Leon Convalescent Center and Local 415-475, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Agreement between Southwest District Council and E Plus E, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Agreement between East Tennessee Undergarment and Local 426, Southern and Western District Council of the Upper South Department, Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Agreement between East Tennessee Undergarment and Local 426, Southern District Council of the Upper South Department, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Collective Bargaining Agreement between Elizabeth Fashions Incorporated and Local Union 408, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Agreement between Embroidery Plus and Joint Board of Cloak, Skirt, and Dressmakers Union, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Collective Bargaining Agreement between Exquisite Form Industries and Southwest District Council, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Agreement between F.L. and J.C. Codman Company and Local 242, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Agreement between F.L. and J.C. Codman Company and Local 242, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Agreement between F.L. and J.C. Codman Company and Local 242, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Agreement between F.L. and J.C. Codman Company and Local 242, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Agreement between F.L. and J.C. Codman Company and Local 242, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Agreement between F.L. and J.C. Codman Company and ILGWU, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Agreement between F.L. and J.C. Codman Company and ILGWU, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Agreement between F.L. and J.C. Codman Company and ILGWU, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Agreement between F.L. and J.C. Codman Company and ILGWU, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Agreement between Fairfield Jersey Incorporated and Local 222, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Agreement between FED Sportswear and Local 585, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Agreement between Faymore Manufacturing Company and Local 445, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Agreement between Faymore Manufacturing Company and Local 445, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Extension Agreement between Fiesta Sportswear Company and Local 261, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Agreement between Filigamme Inc and Quebec Joint Council, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Collective Labor Agreement between Garden State Cutting and ILGWU, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Agreement between Gestion J.L.F. ENRG. And Quebec Joint Council, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  in French
- Agreement between Gerson and Gerson and Local 576, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Agreement between Global Clothing Industries and Local 529, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Agreement between Goodwill Industries and Local 424, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Agreement between Cold Rose and Local 415, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Agreement between Gold Standard Baking and Local 76, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Agreement between Great American Products and Local 76, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Agreement between Griffin Manufacturing Company and Local 178, 1991-1994 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Agreement between Hecht Manufacturing and Local 188, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Agreement between Head Sportswear Division of Leslie Fay Companies and Local 4, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Agreement between Hartford Faience Company and Local 151, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Agreement between Hilson and Missouri-Mississippi River Valley District Council, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Agreements between Hoppe Cutting and Local 111, 1989-1992 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Agreement between House of Charmil and Joint Board of Cloak, Skirt, and Dressmakers Union, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Agreement between Hurlock Sportswear and Local 585, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Agreement between Hygiene Industries and Local 299, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Agreement between Illinois Center for Citizen Involvement and ILGWU, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Agreement between Indiana Sportswear and Local 427, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Agreements between JH Collectibles and Local 188, 1988-1991 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Agreement between JH Collectibles and Local 419, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Agreement between J and J Manufacturing and Local 178, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Agreement between JMJ Fashions and Local 286, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Agreements between Jayo Neckwear and Local 234, 1983-1990 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Agreement between John Wanamaker and Philadelphia-South Jersey District Council, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Agreement between Johnson and Johnson Apparel and Local 576, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Agreement between Jorco Manufacturing and Local 415/475, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Agreement between Joyce Sportswear and Local 449, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Agreement between Kayem Textiles and Local 162, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Agreement between Kelmark and Local 150, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Agreement between Kenwin Shops and Local 122, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Agreement between Key Manufacturing Textiles and Local 111, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Agreement between Kneeland Skirt Company and Joint Board of Cloak, Skirt, and Dressmakers Union, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Agreement between Kords Ambulance Service and Local 512, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Agreement between L + M Industries and Local 600, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Agreement between Lar-Jo Inc and Local 599, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Agreement between Lar-Jo Inc and Local 599, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Agreement between Lawrence Children's Underwear and Local 197, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Agreement between Len-How Corporation and Local 302, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Agreement between Leon Roth/Bridgeport Lingerie and Local 152, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Agreement between Lermer Packaging Corporation and Southwest District Council, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Agreement between Local 101 and La Casa de las Madres, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Agreements between La Manufacture Linge D'Enfants Little Beauty and Quebec Joint Council, 1993-1996 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  in English and French
- Agreement between Lawrence Children's Underwear and Local 197, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Agreement between Les Ateliers Laubia and Quebec Joint Council, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Agreement between Les Confections de Beauce and Quebec Joint Council, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Agreements between Les Elegantes Gaines Alpa and Quebec Joint Council, 1985-1993 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Agreement between Les Nouveautes Berkeley and Quebec Joint Council, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Agreement between Les Produits de Feutre Standard and Quebec Joint Council, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Agreement between Leonard Industries and Local 443, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Agreement between Levine's Inc and Local 261, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Coat and Suit Agreement between Lilli Ann Corporation and Pacific Northwest District Council, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Agreement between Lindy Sportswear and Local 24, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Agreement between Lino Enterprises and Local 109, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Agreements between Liz Claiborne and Local 145, 1986-1995 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Agreement between Liz Claiborne Shoes and Local 130, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Agreement between Liz Claiborne and Local 310, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Agreement between Liz Claiborne Holding Company and Local 109, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Agreements between Lyn-Gai Garment Company and Local 462, 1989-1992 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Agreement between Lyn-Gai Garment Company and Southern Illinois District Council, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Agreement between M.I. Huebschman Company and Local 52, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Agreements with M.I. Huebschman Company and Local 209, 1971-1989 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Agreements between M.I. Huebschman Company and Cleveland Joint Board, 1965-1968 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Agreement between M.I. Phoenix and Local 361, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Agreement between M and R Coat and Local 138, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Agreement between Maidenform and Local 89-22-1, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Agreements between Majestic Lace Corporation and Local 148, 1987-1990 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Agreement between MW Warehouse and Local 132-98-102, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  in Spanish
- Agreement between Main Line Fashions and Local 171, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Agreement between Marcus Manufacturing/Berklee Manufacturing and Local 111, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Agreement between Mared Manufacturing and Local 111, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Agreement between Mariners-Astubeco and Local 162, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Agreement between Mario Valente and Local 141, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Agreement between Marion Manufacturing and Local 567, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Agreement between Catherine G. Mathews Midwest Embroidery and Local 114, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Agreement between Mel's Children's Dress Company and Local 157, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Agreement between Michelle Fashions and Southwest District, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Agreement between Moderama Sportswear and Quebec Joint Council, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Agreement between Modes Me Jay and Quebec Joint Council, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Agreement between Monterey Mills and Local 777, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Agreements between NBC Merchants and Local 399, 1989-1992 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Agreement between National Sportswear Company and Local 553, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Agreements between New England Trading Corporation and Local 313, 1968-1992 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Agreement between Normandy Manufacturing and Local 258, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Agreement between Norminjil Sports and Local 249, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Agreement between Prattville Division of Smoler Brothers and Locals 449 and 382, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Agreement between Plissage Star and Quebec Joint Council, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Agreement between Prive Sportswear and Local 166, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Agreements between Prive Sportswear and Local 166, 1978-1988 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Agreement between Puerto Rican Corset and Brassiere Association and Local 600, 1980-1992 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Agreement between Queenswear International and Quebec Joint Council, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Agreement between R and M Kaufmann and Local 443, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Agreement between Recyclers Consulting Group and Local 151, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Agreement between Reliable Sportswear and Local 178, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Agreements between Rochelle Apparel and Local 178, 1993-1994 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Agreement between Rossmor Industries and Local 171, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Agreements between Robby Len Manufacturing and Local 151, 1988-1997 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Agreements between Robby Len Warehouse and Local 151, 1985-1994 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Agreements between Robby Len Industries and Local 151, 1970-1985 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Agreement between Salon de Coiffure Ahuntsic and Quebec Joint Council, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Agreements between Salisbury Sportswear and Local 445, 1987-1990 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Agreement between Schoolhouse Togs and Local 553, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Agreement between Scotts Hill Leisurewear and Local 478, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Agreement between Sidney Bernstien and Son and Local 197, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Agreement between Simpson Street Cutting and Local 249, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Agreement between Smoler Brothers and Local 76, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Agreement between Sparrow Cutting and Local 234, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Agreement between Spectrum Manufacturing and Local 178, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Agreement between Star Pleating and Quebec Joint Council, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Agreement between State Pleating and Boston Joint Board, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Agreement between Canadian Classique and Local 286, 1995-1996 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Agreement between Stevens Packaging and Local 76, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Agreement between Superior Bias Binding and Textile Company and Southwest District Council, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Agreement between Swanknit and Layettes and Local 163, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Agreements between Sun Apparel and Local 360, 1988-1992 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Agreements between Sun Apparel and Texas-Oklahoma District Council, 1980-1983 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Agreements between T.J. Maxx and Southwest District Council, 1991-1995 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Agreement between Tamac Manufacturing and Local 225, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Agreement between Terry Tuck and Southwest District Council, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Agreement between Theodore Rich and Local 433, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Agreement between The Company Store and Local 379, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Agreement between The Great Put On and Local 317, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Agreement between Tococo and Locals 421 and 422, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Agreements between Triple A in the USA and Local 590, 1986-1993 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Agreement between True-Form Intimate Apparel and Philadelphia/South Jersey District Council, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 11)